<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on @arielsanchezmor blogging here!</title>
    <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on @arielsanchezmor blogging here!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you likes to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 12:20:04 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Links to my VMworld live-tweeting sessions</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/quick-links-to-my-vmworld-live-tweeting-sessions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 12:20:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/quick-links-to-my-vmworld-live-tweeting-sessions/</guid>
      <description>Apologies as I should have put more updates on my blog during VMworld week. I definitely was active on twitter, but Hurricane Dorian was active as soon as I was heading home to Orlando and it took all of my attention. Hurricane Dorian was and still is a big deal - second strongest hurricane to make landfall in the Atlantic basin. Make sure you read up on how you can help the Bahamas and the entire East Coast of the US with donations, as several people&amp;rsquo;s lives have been severely impacted!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More VMworld tips</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/moar-vmworld-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 01:20:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/moar-vmworld-tips/</guid>
      <description>I decided to write additional VMworld tips that I didn&amp;rsquo;t see deeply covered in everyone&amp;rsquo;s blog posts. Better yet, I did it in Github so if anyone wants to add to it, just send me a PR!
https://github.com/arielsanchezmora/More-VMworld-tips/blob/master/README.md
Or, let me know what you think is missing via twitter and I&amp;rsquo;ll add it and credit you.
best,
Ariel</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get ready for the VMworld US 2019 Hackathon, and my team&#39;s details!</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/are-you-ready-for-the-vmworld-us-2019-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 01:20:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/are-you-ready-for-the-vmworld-us-2019-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR: The official VMworld 2019 US hackathon details and public signup will be launched August 12! Make sure to check https://code.vmware.com/home and the VMware Code twitter account
I had explained in a past post why I love VMworld hackathons so much. Reading that post will make it easy to understand my excitement for the upcoming, can&amp;rsquo;t-arrive-soon-enough, VMworld US 2019 Hackathon!
In particular for the VMworld Hackathon events, I recommend you know and follow both VMware communities manager Corey Romero and VMware Code community manager Kripa Sitaraman, as well as the VMware Code twitter account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My love for VMworld hackathons and little hacks</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/my-love-for-vmworld-hackathons-and-little-hacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 01:20:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/my-love-for-vmworld-hackathons-and-little-hacks/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;d like to talk to you today about hackathons. Specifically, a little bit of history, how you can participate, tips on having them in your local community and why I think they are needed. As always on this blog, these are my personal opinions and impressions, not my employer&amp;rsquo;s.
Feedback requested! I welcome all your comments - tweet at me. I&amp;rsquo;d like to expand these ideas in a follow-up blog post and incorporate it into my VMworld vBrownBag TechTalk, so I&amp;rsquo;m looking to improve and include more perspectives on this topic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orlando move completed!</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/orlando-move-completed-and-otheer-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 13:20:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/orlando-move-completed-and-otheer-updates/</guid>
      <description>Man, almost three months without a blog post! Sorry about that, it took us a while to feel like we got everything sorted out. But we&amp;rsquo;re now fully settled in Orlando!
Right after our move, I had to travel a fair bit, which brought on some stress/delays and took away from home time, but in general it has been a smooth transition - thank God for movers, that made everything simpler!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The pursuit of happiness</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/the-pursuit-of-happiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 00:20:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/the-pursuit-of-happiness/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone!
We came to the amazing city of Pittsburgh in 2017 when my wife accepted a learning position in town. Pittsburgh is a city I hold very dear, with genuinely nice people, lots of history and adorable quirks. I will actually make a blog post of all my favorite PGH things in the future. It is a city with excellent craft beer, a hard rock mentality, and true love of sports - who wouldn&amp;rsquo;t love that!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seattle VMUG slides and a quick VSAN post for homelabs</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/seattle-vmug-slides-and-a-quick-vsan-post-for-homelabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:20:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/seattle-vmug-slides-and-a-quick-vsan-post-for-homelabs/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone!
Greetings from Palo Alto! I&amp;rsquo;m here this week for the Office of the CTO Principal/Global Field/Ambassador week-long meeting. I&amp;rsquo;m only one day in, and it&amp;rsquo;s amazing to have this level of access and interaction. Humbled and honored!
Just a week ago, I had the honor of presenting a new talk at the Seattle UserCon on Feb 19. Software Defined Networking is a topic I love geeking out on, but it&amp;rsquo;s not related today with my job at VMware - great material for a community session!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vExpert 2019 - My tips to help your approval odds</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/vexpert-2019---my-tips-to-help-your-approval-odds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 00:20:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/vexpert-2019---my-tips-to-help-your-approval-odds/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: These are Ariel&amp;rsquo;s opinions, born out of my personal experience and not something I have been asked to write by anyone else. I always try to be nice but if any of the following rubs you the wrong way please let me know through twitter
Every 6 months the application period for vExpert comes around. All existing vExperts must re-apply during the January period; new applicants can use either January or July to apply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hug your VMUG leader</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/blogtober-02---hug-your-vmug-leaders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 00:20:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/blogtober-02---hug-your-vmug-leaders/</guid>
      <description>First of all, a reminder that #Blogtober 2018 is ongoing and you still have until today to register! Matt Heldstab&amp;rsquo;s annual call for people to stop slacking and put thoughts to paper is an awesome thing and yes you should participate. Read more about it here: http://tcwd.net/vblog/2018/09/03/blogtober-2018-tech-edition-its-baaack/. It&amp;rsquo;s not even about the gift cards, it&amp;rsquo;s just that extra push to share more of who you are, what you like and what you do as part of the #vCommunity</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Blogtober 2018, PKS Roadshows, vForum online</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/blogtober-01---welcome-to-blogtober-pks-roadshows-vforum-online-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 00:20:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/blogtober-01---welcome-to-blogtober-pks-roadshows-vforum-online-/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to #Blogtober 2018! If you haven&amp;rsquo;t noticed yet, Matt Heldstab&amp;rsquo;s annual call for people to stop slacking and put thoughts to paper is alive! Read more about it here: http://tcwd.net/vblog/2018/09/03/blogtober-2018-tech-edition-its-baaack/ There&amp;rsquo;s still ample time to register, so just do it k?
Today is a short entry, but a time sensitive one. We have two free events, one multi-city and one virtual next week. Most importantly, the multi-city comes to my hometown Pittsburgh this Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMworld 2018 whirlwind starts!</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/whirlwind-to-vmworld-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 00:20:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/whirlwind-to-vmworld-2018/</guid>
      <description>Hello hello :)
As the biggest party in my calendar year is upon us, I wanted to make a &amp;ldquo;100% true to everything I want to do&amp;rdquo; public google calendar, but I also feel like there&amp;rsquo;s some things I&amp;rsquo;d like to write in a blog post and point out that may help anyone reading this.
My public calendar has about everything I have planned and can be found here: https://sites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LittleHack005 - The day we got more than 3 people!</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/littlehack005/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:20:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/littlehack005/</guid>
      <description>Hello again!
This is a post for me to state that I&amp;rsquo;m happy! We got 6, yes SIX people to come today :)
Jean-Pierre Nsanzabera
Matt Puthoff
John Devine
Carl Capozza
Thomas Higgins
You can find pictures with the #PGHLittleHack hashtag, and you can read more about it in Carl&amp;rsquo;s blog and the post in vbrownbag.com. To attend and be involved / notified of future ones, give us a shout out in Twitter!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#DVVMUG and #WIVMUG slide decks</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/2018-04-denver-and-wisconsin-vmug-decks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 07:09:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/2018-04-denver-and-wisconsin-vmug-decks/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone, happy end of April!
I&amp;rsquo;ve just created a new repo and uploaded the presentations for the VMUG UserCons that sponsored me as a vCommunity speaker. You can find them here:
https://github.com/arielsanchezmora/VMUG-Talks
Best,
Ariel</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#sddcroadshow coming in May! DR focused event</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/2018-04-sddc-dr-roadshow-coming-in-may/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 07:09:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/2018-04-sddc-dr-roadshow-coming-in-may/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone, happy middle of April!
I recently heard from Brant Scalan (@fatpacket on twitter) that he and John Whitman (@VCDX226) are running a SDDC Roadshow coming up in 8 mayor cities in the month of May. It brought me memories of when I went to my first VMworld roadshow, and how great it was - this was ages ago, before I had even gone to a VMUG!
What I really love about these events is that they are organized as a workshop focused on one topic, and it&amp;rsquo;s basically a full day agenda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#vCommunity VMworld 2018 submissions</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/2018-04-vcommunity-vmworld-submissions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 07:09:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/2018-04-vcommunity-vmworld-submissions/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone, happy April!
These past weeks several VMUG leaders were greeted with the news that they had been selected for the VMworld session private voting panel. I voted on this panel when I was a leader and I really enjoyed being able to read all submissions and influence my point of view into the final &amp;ldquo;menu&amp;rdquo;. By the way, the voting time has even been extended to April 13th!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, you want to play with #VRDCEX?</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/2018-01-hey-you-want-to-play-with-vr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 07:09:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/2018-01-hey-you-want-to-play-with-vr/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone, happy February!
This February 27 we will have a most fabulous Pittsburgh UserCon, where a lot of friends from the #vCommunity will come and we will have a jolly time geeking out on all things VMware. I could go on and on about who&amp;rsquo;s coming and what the VMUG leaders have prepared, but that will be another post ;)
This post is to let you know that tomorrow, February 13, I will be playing with aDell Mixed VR headset, getting it ready so that we can have UserCon attendees play with #VRDCEX at the UserCon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vBrownBag - End of 2017 posts</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/vbrownbag---end-of-2017-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 22:09:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/vbrownbag---end-of-2017-posts/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone, happy holidays :)
This is a blog post to highlight a new entry in the super cool, so awesome you should read more of it, vBrownbag blog:
Meet the expert interviews at @wpvmug and @cincivmug 2017Q4.
I really enjoy filming these. There&amp;rsquo;s so many awesome people in the #vCommunity that I admire and I&amp;rsquo;ve met through twitter/VMUG/VMworld/Slack, but almost always don&amp;rsquo;t have the time and one-to-one focus to really get to know them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fedora 27 dual boot with Windows 10 and UEFI - Learning in IT</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/fedora-27-dual-boot-with-windows-10-and-uefi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 22:09:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/fedora-27-dual-boot-with-windows-10-and-uefi/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone!
This is a quick blog post to highlight a new entry in my Learning-in-IT.blogspot.com blog:
Installing Fedora 27 on a UEFI-enabled Windows 10 machine with Secure Boot enabled.
I hope you find it useful if you are in the same situation. I really think learning Linux/BSD is key to my future in IT, so I&amp;rsquo;m renewing my efforts to use it as my main OS and for studying for the LFCS exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disabling vSAN and reclaiming disks when vCenter is not available - VM Gotchas</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/disabling-vsan-and-reclaiming-disks-when-vcenter-is-not-available/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 21:09:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/disabling-vsan-and-reclaiming-disks-when-vcenter-is-not-available/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone!
This is a quick blog post to highlight a new entry in my VMGotchas.com blog:
Disabling vSAN and reclaiming disks when vCenter is not available. I hope you enjoy it!
Let me know your comments in Twitter @arielsanchezmor. Thank you for reading, and hope to see you around soon!
Ariel</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#vDocumentation, three months in</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/vdocumentation-three-months-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 10:09:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/vdocumentation-three-months-in/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone!
This is a retrospective blog post on the little open source project that Edgar Sanchez @edmsanchez13 and I launched in VMworld US 2017 named #vDocumentation
We submitted it as a session in VMworld 2017 and we were very happy to see that 1) it was approved 2) it was a popular session! It was pretty neat that we got a 500 person room on Monday after the keynote, because people are very anxious to go into sessions at that point of the conference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing abstracts for IT conferences</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/writing-abstracts-for-conferences/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 09:11:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/writing-abstracts-for-conferences/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone,
I was chatting with my good friend Nick Scuola @nscuola. He&amp;rsquo;s going to submit some talks for ZertoCon and mentioned he should read advice for writing abstracts. I offered him my experience, and it suddenly hit me that I should make a blog post about it, so it can help others.
I went through one denial and one approval, for what in my mind were very similar talks, but I changed the abstract quite a lot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git Cheat Sheet - learning in IT</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/git-cheat-sheet-post---from-learning-in-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 23:20:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/git-cheat-sheet-post---from-learning-in-it/</guid>
      <description>Hey! It&amp;rsquo;s your noob friend Ariel sharing what little he&amp;rsquo;s learned - exactly the one-eyes leading the blind :)
Carl Capozza has done an excellent job of helping me get accustomed to using Git comands. I actually taught someone in the #PGHLittleHack 1.3 what I learned today and they were able to get it to work, and they were happy! So here I am sharing the blog post I did. Please let me know if anything isn&amp;rsquo;t clear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LittleHack003 - If you build it they will come!</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/littlehack003/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 00:20:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/littlehack003/</guid>
      <description>Hello again!
This is a post for me to state that I&amp;rsquo;m very, very happy! It&amp;rsquo;s crazy that something that started with just &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rsquo;d like to get this feeling again, how do we do it?&amp;rdquo; has become an event that three people travelled several miles to assist! The PGH LittleHack really had an all-star crowd for its 3rd incarnation:
Kyle Ruddy
Justin Sider
Dan Barr
AJ Kuftic
Doug DeFrank
David Kalaluhi</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final Pittsburgh VMUG details October 20</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/final-pgh-vmug-details-oct-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 00:15:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/final-pgh-vmug-details-oct-20/</guid>
      <description>Hello again! Just doing a small post here to highlight I contributed a post for the Western PA VMUG Blog. After all, I did commit to #Blogtober, and I did tell you I would centralize my blogging activity in one place so Azarya can find it.
The post is the final speaker details for the upcoming Pittsburgh VMUG this October 20. I&amp;rsquo;m not a leader anymore like I was in NYC, since I&amp;rsquo;m a VMware employee now; but one thing we should always understand is anybody can help without the title.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ariel&#39;s blogging</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/consolidated_blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 00:15:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/consolidated_blogging/</guid>
      <description>Hello again! Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about blogging - in particular, say, I don&amp;rsquo;t know, my blogging :)
Blogging is cool. It&amp;rsquo;s also not that hard. You don&amp;rsquo;t have to write a long essay - it shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be tweet-sized either, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t need to be too long. Take a little while to share something, even if it&amp;rsquo;s just a piece of your mind.
I particularly like focused blogs that solve some kind of problem most.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LittleHack002</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/littlehack002/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 00:20:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/littlehack002/</guid>
      <description>Hello again!
You can&amp;rsquo;t learn what you can&amp;rsquo;t repeat. So here I am making a second blog post with Hugo on my Github page with a custom domain to get into the groove.
We&amp;rsquo;re doing another #PGHLittleHack this Thursday, October 5. If you don&amp;rsquo;t remember what they are about @CarlCapozza and I started doing a local, VMUG/vBrownBag version, of the VMworld Hackathons, right after the 2017 VMworld US Hackathon - because we loved the concept, camaraderie, and knowledge sharing spirit of it, and we wanted more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LittleHack001</title>
      <link>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/littlehack001/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 00:20:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blogs.arielsanchezmora.com/post/littlehack001/</guid>
      <description>Hi Gang!
It took me a while to figure out how to create a custom domain using the Hugo static website generator, but here we are!
This was part of the #PGHLittleHack initiative that @CarlCapozza and I started right after the 2017 VMworld US Hackathon.
Thank you for reading this! It&amp;rsquo;s obviously a small start but I&amp;rsquo;m proud of it :)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>